## **CONTACT**

- ≤ contact@remijonathan.com
- **(**514) 664-6333
- **9** 4406 Saint-Jacques, Montréal
- premijonathan.com

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Professional Scrum Master I
- Professional Scrum Master II

# **SKILLS**

- Scrum framework expertise
- In-depth knowledge of Agile
- Expertise in planning 8 ensuring
  efficient use of resources
- Excellent communication & interpersonal skills
- Proficiency in Java, Python, and other modern programming language.
- Experience with Git, Jira, and Confluence

## **LANGUAGES**

- English Perfectly bilingual
- French Perfectly bilingual

# RJ CHOQUETTE

Professional Scrum Master & Agile Project Manager

I am an accomplished Scrum Master and Agile expert with a passion for making a positive impact on the world. With exceptional problemsolving skills, I excel at identifying the root cause of issues within applications and determining modifications.

My planning competencies allow me to oversee multiple projects simultaneously, ensuring deadlines are met and stakeholders are satisfied. I have strong project management skills, including risk oversight, requirements gathering, and scope development.

I have excellent communication and interpersonal skills, which have enabled me to work effectively with product owners, team members, technologists, and other Scrum Masters. I am committed to using my skills to make a positive impact on the world and I am confident that I can make a valuable contribution to any organization.

#### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

Computer Science & Business Champlain College | May 2020

• Computer Science Department Tutor

#### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND - CONTINUED**

# BA Business Technology Management

John Molson School of Business | Part-Time | On Going

 Looking to hone my skills in project management and business skills to eventually enter into an MBA

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

# Scrum Master & Programmer Analyst

Desjardins | May 2018 - present

- Key player in the creation of systems handling north of 3 million dollars in transactions daily
- Created systems to optimize mortgage rates for clients enabling us to have a competitive edge over other financial institutions.
- Facilitated Scrum framework, including sprint planning, backlog grooming, daily scrums, sprint reviews, and sprint retrospectives.
- Led sprint reviews, daily scrums, and planning meetings to ensure full team engagement.
- Managed the product backlog and supported the Scrum framework for bi-weekly sprint releases.
- Collaborated with product owners, team members, technologists, and other Scrum Masters to define solutions and drive progress.

## Vice President of Financial Affairs

ECA Concordia | May 2021 - April 2023

- Managed the association's budget
- Prepared financial reports and presented them at meetings
- Actively participated in the decision-making process for the association

## Bank of Montreal

Associate Banker | Jul 2016 - May 2018

- Visited corporate client offices to offer the latest products
- Reviewed customer profiles proactively to warm call them about how they could benefit from additional services and boost sales by 63%
- Built relationships with clients to maintain sales goals and create new opportunities